<Database>
    <GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_MORE_DG_DIAGNOSES">

        <LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
        <LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>

        <Contributors>
			<Name></Name>
        </Contributors>

        <LocalizedStrings>

			<!-- ================================================== Clinique ================================================== -->
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_RA</LocID>												<Text>Aortic stenosis</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_RA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>									<Text>Aortic stenosis is one of the most common and most serious valve disease problems. Aortic stenosis is a narrowing of the aortic valve opening. Aortic stenosis restricts the blood flow from the left ventricle to the aorta and may also affect the pressure in the left atrium.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_IA</LocID>												<Text>Aortic insufficiency</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_IA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>									<Text>Aortic insufficiency (AI), also known as aortic regurgitation (AR), is the leaking of the aortic valve of the heart that causes blood to flow in the reverse direction during ventricular diastole, from the aorta into the left ventricle. As a consequence, the cardiac muscle is forced to work harder than normal.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_SYNCOPE_NC</LocID>										<Text>Neurocardiogenic syncope</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_SYNCOPE_NC_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>Syncope is a brief loss of consciousness (BLC) due to rapid onset cerebral hypoperfusion, of short duration and complete and spontaneous recovery. After the event, the neurological state (including behavior and orientation) is normal. The patient has no recorded memories during the BLC period.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HYPOTA_ORTHO</LocID>										<Text>Orthostatic hypotension</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HYPOTA_ORTHO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>Orthostatic hypotension is defined as a decrease in systolic blood pressure of 20 mm Hg or a decrease in diastolic blood pressure of 10 mm Hg within three minutes of standing when compared with blood pressure from the sitting or supine position.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_SD_STOKESADAMS</LocID>									<Text>Adams–Stokes syndrome</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_SD_STOKESADAMS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Sudden collapse into unconsciousness due to a disorder of heart rhythm in which there is a slow or absent pulse resulting in syncope (fainting) with or without convulsions. In this condition, the normal heartbeat passing from the upper chambers of the heart to the lower chambers is interrupted.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_LIPOTHYMIE</LocID>										<Text>Presyncope</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_LIPOTHYMIE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>Lightheadedness can also be called presyncope, in contrast with syncope (fainting), particularly in cases of temporary visual field loss. Lightheadedness is a common and typically unpleasant sensation of dizziness or a feeling that one may faint. The sensation of lightheadedness can be short-lived, prolonged, or, rarely, recurring. In addition to dizziness, the individual may feel as though his or her head is weightless. The individual may also feel as though the room is "spinning" or moving (vertigo) associated with lightheadedness. Most causes of lightheadedness are not serious and either cure themselves quickly, or are easily treated.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_FIBRILLATION_ATRIALE</LocID>								<Text>Atrial fibrillation</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_FIBRILLATION_ATRIALE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					<Text>Atrial fibrillation (AF or A-fib) is an abnormal heart rhythm (arrhythmia) characterized by rapid and irregular beating of the atrial chambers of the heart.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_DYSFONCTION_SINUSALE</LocID>								<Text>Sick Sinus Syndrome</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_DYSFONCTION_SINUSALE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					<Text>Sick sinus syndrome (SSS), is a group of abnormal heart rhythms (arrhythmias) presumably caused by a malfunction of the sinus node, the heart's primary pacemaker. Tachycardia-bradycardia syndrome is a variant of sick sinus syndrome in which the arrhythmia alternates between slow and fast heart rates. Tachycardia-bradycardia syndrome is often associated with ischemic heart disease and heart valve disease.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_BLOC_ATRIOVENTRICULAIRE</LocID>							<Text>Atrioventricular block</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_BLOC_ATRIOVENTRICULAIRE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Atrioventricular block (AV block) is a type of heart block that occurs when the electrical signal traveling from the atria, or the upper chambers of the heart, to ventricles, or the lower chambers of the heart, is impaired. Normally, the sinoatrial node (SA node) produces an electrical signal to control the heart rate. The signal travels from the SA node to the ventricles through the atrioventricular node (AV node). In an AV block, this electrical signal is either delayed or completely blocked. When the signal is completely blocked, the ventricles produce their own electrical signal to control the heart rate. The heart rate produced by the ventricles is much slower than that produced by the SA node.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_BB_GAUCHE</LocID>											<Text>Left bundle branch block</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_BB_GAUCHE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>								<Text>Left bundle branch block (LBBB) is a cardiac conduction abnormality seen on the electrocardiogram (ECG). In this condition, activation of the left ventricle of the heart is delayed, which causes the left ventricle to contract later than the right ventricle.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_TACHYCARDIE_VENTRICULAIRE</LocID>							<Text>Ventricular tachycardia</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_TACHYCARDIE_VENTRICULAIRE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Ventricular tachycardia (V-tach or VT) is a type of regular, fast heart rate that arises from improper electrical activity in the ventricles of the heart.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_BOUVERET</LocID>											<Text>Bouveret-Hoffmann syndrome</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_BOUVERET_DESCRIPTION</LocID>								<Text>It is a rapid heartbeat that originates neither from the atria nor the ventricles, but rather from a node responsible for the propagation of electrical impulses of the heart.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_TORSADE_DE_POINTES</LocID>								<Text>Torsade de pointes</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_TORSADE_DE_POINTES_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					<Text>Torsades de pointes (TdP) (translated as "twisting of peaks"), is a specific type of abnormal heart rhythm that can lead to sudden cardiac death. It is a polymorphic ventricular tachycardia that exhibits distinct characteristics on the electrocardiogram (ECG). It was described by Frenchman François Dessertenne in 1966.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_SD_WPW</LocID>											<Text>Wolff–Parkinson–White syndrome</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_SD_WPW_DESCRIPTION</LocID>								<Text>Wolff–Parkinson–White syndrome (WPWS) is a disorder due to a specific type of problem with the electrical system of the heart which has resulted in symptoms.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_MDG_ICG</LocID>											<Text>Left-sides heath failure</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_MDG_ICG_DESCRIPTION</LocID>								<Text>Left-sided heart failure occurs when the left ventricle doesn't pump efficiently.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_MDG_ICD</LocID>											<Text>Right-sided heath failure</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_MDG_ICD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>								<Text>Righ-sided heart failure occurs when the right ventricle doesn't pump efficiently.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_AOMI</LocID>												<Text>OALL</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_AOMI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>									<Text>Obliterating Arteriopathy of the Lower Limbs (OALL) is defined as partial or total atheromatous obstruction of one or more arteries intended for the lower limbs.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ANEVRISME_AAA</LocID>										<Text>AAA</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ANEVRISME_AAA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>Abdominal aortic aneurysm (AAA) is a localized enlargement of the abdominal aorta such that the diameter is greater than 3 cm or more than 50% larger than normal.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ANEVRISME_POPLITE</LocID>									<Text>PAAs</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ANEVRISME_POPLITE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Popliteal artery aneurysms (PAAs) is bulging and weakness in the wall of the popliteal artery, which supplies blood to the knee joint, thigh and calf.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ISCHEMIE_MESENTERIQUE_CHRONIQUE</LocID>					<Text>Chronic mesenteric ischemia</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ISCHEMIE_MESENTERIQUE_CHRONIQUE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>		<Text>Chronic digestive ischemia affects the elderly; it predominates in women in more than 70% of cases. This pathology is uncommon and indicates an advanced and diffuse atheromatous disease.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
<!-- v0.02  -->
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_DALA</LocID>											<Text>PADAM</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_DALA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>								<Text>The term "andropause" is commonly used to refer to the decline in circulating testosterone from the age of 40 in men. Another popular term is that of "hypogonadism" in the elderly or partial androgen deficiency in the elderly - known by the acronym PADAM (Partial Androgen Deficiency in Aged Male).</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HPRL_F</LocID>										<Text>Hyperprolactinemia</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HPRL_H</LocID>										<Text>Hyperprolactinemia</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HPRL_DESCRIPTION</LocID>								<Text>Prolactin is a peptide hormone produced by the anterior pituitary gland that is primarily associated with lactation and plays a vital role in breast development during pregnancy. Hyperprolactinaemia may cause galactorrhea (production and spontaneous flow of breast milk), infertility, and disruptions in the normal menstrual period in women; and hypogonadism, infertility and erectile dysfunction in men.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ACROMEGALIE</LocID>									<Text>Acromegaly</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ACROMEGALIE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Acromegaly is a disorder that results from excess growth hormone (GH) after the growth plates have closed.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_CUSHING_F</LocID>										<Text>Cushing's disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_CUSHING_H</LocID>										<Text>Cushing's disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_CUSHING_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>Cushing's disease is one cause of Cushing's syndrome characterised by increased secretion of adrenocorticotropic hormone (ACTH) from the anterior pituitary (secondary hypercortisolism). This is most often as a result of a pituitary adenoma (specifically pituitary basophilism) or due to excess production of hypothalamus CRH (corticotropin releasing hormone) (tertiary hypercortisolism/hypercorticism) that stimulates the synthesis of cortisol by the adrenal glands.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ADN_THYREOTRP</LocID>									<Text>Central hyperthyroidism</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ADN_THYREOTRP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Central hyperthyroidism is caused by the overproduction of thyroid hormones from pituitary gland. TSH (Thyroid Stimulating Hormone) is a hormone secreted by the anterior part of the pituitary gland. TSH will be produced in excess in the presence of an adenoma sitting in this specific area. TSH will over-stimulate the thyroid gland, located at the base of the neck, resulting in hypersecretion of thyroid hormones.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_PAN_HYPOPT_F</LocID>									<Text>Anterior pituitary insufficiency syndrome</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_PAN_HYPOPT_H</LocID>									<Text>Anterior pituitary insufficiency syndrome</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_PAN_HYPOPT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Syndrome characterized by a deficiency of all the anterior pituitary hormones (panhypopituitarism). The presence of a pituitary adenoma can be at the origin of an anterior pituitary insufficiency.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ADDISON_F</LocID>										<Text>Addison's disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ADDISON_H</LocID>										<Text>Addison's disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ADDISON_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>Addison's disease, also known as primary adrenal insufficiency and hypocortisolism, is a long-term endocrine disorder in which the adrenal glands do not produce enough steroid hormones.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_BLOC_ENZ_F</LocID>									<Text>21-OH enzyme block</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_BLOC_ENZ_H</LocID>									<Text>21-OH enzyme block</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_BLOC_ENZ_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>These are autosomal recessive diseases linked to a mutation in a gene encoding an enzyme of steroidogenesis. The gene by far most often involved is the one encoding 21-hydroxylase (21-hydroxylase deficiency). Cortisol and aldosterone are not synthesized normally, hence the adrenal insufficiency.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ICT</LocID>											<Text>Corticotropic insufficiency</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ICT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>								<Text>Central adrenal insufficiency, or corticotropic insufficiency is from pituitary or hypothalamic causes or following the discontinuation of prolonged corticosteroid therapy (the most frequent cause). Aldosterone secretion is preserved, which explains a usually less severe picture.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HYPO_PT_AA</LocID>									<Text>Autoimmune hypoparathyroidism</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HYPO_PT_AA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Hypoparathyroidism is a rare condition in which the parathyroid glands fail to produce sufficient amounts of parathyroid hormone or the parathyroid hormone produced lacks biologic activity. The parathyroid glands are part of the endocrine system, the network of glands that secrete hormones into the bloodstream where they travel to various areas of the body. These hormones regulate the chemical processes (metabolism) that influence the function of various organs and activities within the body.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HYPER_PT</LocID>										<Text>Primary hyperparathyroidism</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HYPER_PT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>Hyperparathyroidism is an increase in parathyroid hormone (PTH) levels in the blood. When this occurs from a disorder either within the parathyroid glands it's called primary hyperparathyroidism.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_CONN</LocID>											<Text>Conn's syndrome</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_CONN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>								<Text>Primary aldosteronism, also known as primary hyperaldosteronism or Conn's syndrome, refers to the excess production of the hormone aldosterone from the adrenal glands, resulting in low renin levels. Conn's adenoma is a benign tumor of the adrenal cortex.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HBL_SRN</LocID>										<Text>Bilateral adrenal hyperplasia</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HBL_SRN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>In bilateral hyperplasia, the excessive and uncontrolled production of aldosterone depends on the two adrenal glands.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_INSULINOME</LocID>									<Text>Insulinoma</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_INSULINOME_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>An insulinoma is a tumor of the pancreas that is derived from beta cells and secretes insulin. It is a rare form of a neuroendocrine tumor. Most insulinomas are benign in that they grow exclusively at their origin within the pancreas, but a minority metastasize.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_SD_HGP</LocID>										<Text>NIPHS</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_SD_HGP_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>Noninsulinoma pancreatogenous hypoglycemia syndrome (NIPHS) is a rare syndrome characterized by endogenous hyperinsulinemic hypoglycemia that is not caused by an insulinoma.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_QUERVAIN</LocID>										<Text>De Quervain's thyroiditis</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_QUERVAIN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>De Quervain's thyroiditis, also known as subacute granulomatous thyroiditis or giant cell thyroiditis, is a member of the group of thyroiditis conditions known as resolving thyroiditis.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_GOITRE_MULTINODULE</LocID>							<Text>Toxic multinodular goiter</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_GOITRE_MULTINODULE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Toxic multinodular goiter is the natural evolution of ancient multinodular goiter.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ADENOME_TOXIQUE</LocID>								<Text>Plummer's toxic adenoma</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ADENOME_TOXIQUE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					<Text>The toxic adenoma is a solitary, hyperfunctional benign tumor of the thyroid. This pathology indicates the presence of a localized hypertrophy from where the appearance of a protuberance of generally rounded shape. In addition, this type of adenoma is distinguished by its autonomous functioning.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
<!-- v0.03  -->
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_PORPHYRIE</LocID>								<Text>AIP</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_PORPHYRIE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					<Text>Acute intermittent porphyria (AIP) is a rare autosomal dominant metabolic disorder affecting the production of heme resulting from a deficiency of the porphobilinogen deaminase. It is the most common of the acute porphyrias.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_SPHEROCYTOSE</LocID>							<Text>Minkowski-Chauffard disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_SPHEROCYTOSE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Minkowski-Chauffard disease or Hereditary spherocytosis is an abnormality of red blood cells, or erythrocytes. The disorder is caused by mutations in genes relating to membrane proteins that allow for the erythrocytes to change shape. The abnormal erythrocytes are sphere-shaped (spherocytosis) rather than the normal biconcave disk shaped.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_MARCHIAFAVA_MICHELI</LocID>					<Text>Marchiafava Micheli syndrome</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_MARCHIAFAVA_MICHELI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>		<Text>Marchiafava Micheli syndrome or Paroxysmal nocturnal hemoglobinuria (PNH) is a rare, acquired, life-threatening disease of the blood characterized by destruction of red blood cells by the complement system, a part of the body's innate immune system.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_FAVISME</LocID>								<Text>Favism</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_FAVISME_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					<Text>Favism or Glucose-6-phosphate dehydrogenase deficiency (G6PDD) is an inborn error of metabolism that predisposes to red blood cell breakdown.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_DEFICIT_PK</LocID>							<Text>PK deficiency</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_DEFICIT_PK_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Pyruvate kinase deficiency is an inherited metabolic disorder of the enzyme pyruvate kinase which affects the survival of red blood cells.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_AHAA</LocID>									<Text>AIHA</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_AHAA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Autoimmune hemolytic anemia (AIHA) occurs when antibodies directed against the person's own red blood cells (RBCs) cause them to burst (lyse), leading to an insufficient number of oxygen-carrying red blood cells in the circulation.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_PTT</LocID>									<Text>Moschkowitz disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_PTT_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Moschkowitz disease or Thrombotic thrombocytopenic purpura (TTP) is a blood disorder that results in blood clots forming in small blood vessels throughout the body.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_DREPA_A</LocID>								<Text>Acute sickle cell disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_DREPA_C</LocID>								<Text>Chronic sickle cell disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_DREPA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>La drépanocytose, aussi appelée anémie falciforme, est une maladie héréditaire touchant l'hémoglobine des globules rouges.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_WILLEBRAND</LocID>							<Text>vWD</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_WILLEBRAND_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Von Willebrand disease (vWD) is the most common hereditary blood-clotting disorder in humans. It arises from a deficiency in the quality or quantity of von Willebrand factor (vWF), a multimeric protein that is required for platelet adhesion.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
<!-- v0.03.2  -->
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_NIEMANN-PICK</LocID>								<Text>Niemann-Pick disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_NIEMANN-PICK_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					<Text>Niemann-Pick disease type C (NP-C) is a lysosomal lipid storage disease.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_KIMURA</LocID>									<Text>Kimura disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_KIMURA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Kimura disease is a benign and chronic inflammatory disorder of unknown etiology, occurring mainly in Asian countries (very rarely in Western countries) and predominantly affecting young men.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_FANCONI</LocID>									<Text>Fanconi anemia</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_FANCONI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Fanconi anemia (FA) is a hereditary DNA repair disorder. FA is due to mutations in genes involved in DNA repair and genomic stability. Fifteen genes representing 15 complementation groups have been identified.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_BERNARD-SOULIER</LocID>							<Text>Bernard-Soulier syndrome</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_BERNARD-SOULIER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Bernard Soulier syndrome (BSS) is an inherited platelet disorder characterized by mild to severe bleeding tendency , macrothrombocytopenia and absent ristocetin-induced platelet agglutination.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_THROMBASTHENIE_GLANDZMANN</LocID>					<Text>Glanzmann thrombasthenia</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_THROMBASTHENIE_GLANDZMANN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>		<Text>Glanzmann thrombasthenia (GT) is a bleeding syndrome characterized by spontaneous mucocutaneous bleeding and an exaggerated response to trauma due to a constitutional thrombocytopenia.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ANEMIE_BLACKFAN_DIAMOND</LocID>					<Text>Blackfan-Diamond anemia</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ANEMIE_BLACKFAN_DIAMOND_DESCRIPTION</LocID>		<Text>Blackfan-Diamond anemia (DBA) is a congenital aregenerative and often macrocytic anemia with erythroblastopenia. At present, disease-causing mutations are identified in 40-45% of patients. All involved genes code for ribosomal proteins (RPs).</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_MALADIE_GAUCHER</LocID>							<Text>Gaucher disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_MALADIE_GAUCHER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Gaucher disease (GD) is a lysosomal storage disorder encompassing three main forms (types 1, 2 and 3), a fetal form and a variant with cardiac involvement (Gaucher disease - ophthalmoplegia - cardiovascular calcification or Gaucher-like disease). GD is due to mutations in the GBA gene (1q21) that codes for a lysosomal enzyme, glucocerebrosidase, or in very rare cases the PSAP gene that codes for its activator protein (saposin C). The deficiency in glucocerebrosidase leads to the accumulation of glucosylceramidase (or beta-glucocerebrosidase) deposits in the cells of the reticuloendothelial system of the liver, the spleen and the bone marrow (Gaucher cells).</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_MALADIE_DUNCAN</LocID>							<Text>Duncan disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_MALADIE_DUNCAN_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Duncan disease or Purtilo syndrome or X-linked lymphoproliferative disease is a primary immune deficiency linked to cellular immune deficiencies.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ASIA</LocID>										<Text>AISA</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ASIA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>Acquired idiopathic sideroblastic anemia (AISA) is a rare myelodysplastic syndrome (MDS) characterized by ineffective hemopoiesis affecting one or more blood cell lineages (myeloid, erythroid or megakaryocytic) leading to peripheral blood cytopenias and an increased risk of developing leukaemia.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ERYTHROBLASTOPENIE_ISO</LocID>					<Text>Isolated erythroblastopenia</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_ERYTHROBLASTOPENIE_ISO_DESCRIPTION</LocID>		<Text>It is an acute blood disorder characterized by the decrease or disappearance of erythroblasts (bone marrow cells specialized in the synthesis of hemoglobin) and resulting in anemia.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOGLOBINOSE_C</LocID>							<Text>Hemoglobin C disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOGLOBINOSE_C_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Hemoglobin C disease (HbC) is a hemoglobinopathy characterized by production of abnormal variant hemoglobin known as hemoglobin C.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOGLOBINOSE_D</LocID>							<Text>Hemoglobin D disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOGLOBINOSE_D_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Hemoglobin D disease (HbD) is a hemoglobinopathy characterized by production of abnormal variant hemoglobin known as hemoglobin D.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOGLOBINOSE_E</LocID>							<Text>Hemoglobin E disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOGLOBINOSE_E_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Hemoglobin E disease (HbE) is a hemoglobinopathy characterized by production of abnormal variant hemoglobin known as hemoglobin E.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOGLOBINOSE_M</LocID>							<Text>Hemoglobin M disease</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOGLOBINOSE_M_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Hemoglobin M disease (HbM) is a hemoglobinopathy characterized by production of abnormal variant hemoglobin known as hemoglobin M.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_PLUMMER_VINSON</LocID>							<Text>Plummer-Vinson syndrome</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_PLUMMER_VINSON_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Plummer-Vinson or Paterson-Kelly syndrome presents as a classical triad of dysphagia, iron-deficiency anemia and esophageal webs. The etiopathogenesis of Plummer-Vinson syndrome is unknown. The most important possible etiological factor is iron deficiency. Other possible factors include malnutrition, genetic predisposition or autoimmune processes.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_RENDU_OSLER_WEBER</LocID>							<Text>HHT</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_RENDU_OSLER_WEBER_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Rendu-Osler-Weber disease or Hereditary Hemorrhagic Telangiectasia (HHT) is an inherited disorder of angiogenesis characterized by mucocutaneous telangiectases and visceral arteriovenous malformations. This genetic disorder is due to pathogenic variants primarily in ENG or ACVRL1, encoding proteins involved in vascular development and angiogenic homeostasis of capillaries.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_SD_EVANS</LocID>									<Text>Evans syndrome</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_SD_EVANS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>A rare chronic hematologic disorder characterized by the simultaneous or sequential association of autoimmune hemolytic anemia with immune thrombocytopenic purpura and occasionally autoimmune neutropenia, in the absence of a known underlying etiology.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOCHROMATOSE_1</LocID>							<Text>Hemochromatosis type 1</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOCHROMATOSE_1_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Symptomatic form of hemochromatosis type 1 is a rare, hereditary hemochromatosis characterized by inappropriately regulated intestinal iron absorption which leads to excessive iron storage in various organs and manifests with a wide range of signs and symptoms.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOCHROMATOSE_2</LocID>							<Text>Hemochromatosis type 2</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOCHROMATOSE_2_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Hemochromatosis type 2 (juvenile) is the early-onset and most severe form of rare hereditary hemochromatosis (HH), a group of diseases characterized by excessive tissue iron deposition of genetic origin.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOCHROMATOSE_3</LocID>							<Text>Hemochromatosis type 3</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOCHROMATOSE_3_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Type 3 hemochromatosis is a form of rare hereditary hemochromatosis (HH), a group of diseases characterized by excessive tissue iron deposition of genetic origin.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOCHROMATOSE_4</LocID>							<Text>Hemochromatosis type 4</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_HEMOCHROMATOSE_4_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Hemochromatosis type 4 (also called ferroportin disease) is a form of rare hereditary hemochromatosis (HH), a group of diseases characterized by excessive tissue iron deposition of genetic origin.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_APLASIE_MÉDULLAIRE_IDIOPATHIQUE</LocID>			<Text>Idiopathic aplastic anemia</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>DIA_MOREDG_APLASIE_MÉDULLAIRE_IDIOPATHIQUE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>	<Text>Idiopathic bone marrow failure or Idiopathic aplastic anemia is an inability of the bone marrow to replace blood cells as they die naturally. It results in a deficit in the production of one or more types of cells normally found in the blood. The name "idiopathic" means that the cause is unknown.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			

			<!-- ================================================== Urgences ================================================== -->

			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_URGENCE_HTA</LocID>									<Text>Hypertensive emergency</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_URGENCE_HTA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Hypertensive emergency is characterized by hypertension, most often severe (or quickly installed in a normotensive patient) and which is associated with acute damage to the target organs.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_ISCHEMIE_MS</LocID>									<Text>Acute ischemia of the upper limb</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_ISCHEMIE_MS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Acute limb ischaemia occurs when there is a sudden lack of blood flow to a limb.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_ISCHEMIE_MI</LocID>									<Text>Acute ischemia of the lower limb</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_ISCHEMIE_MI_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Acute limb ischaemia occurs when there is a sudden lack of blood flow to a limb.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_ISCHEMIE_MESENTERIQUE</LocID>							<Text>Acute mesenteric ischemia</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_ISCHEMIE_MESENTERIQUE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Mesenteric ischemia is a medical condition in which injury to the small intestine occurs due to not enough blood supply, it's associated with a high risk of death.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_RUPTURE_AAA</LocID>									<Text>Abdominal Aortic Aneurysm Rupture</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_RUPTURE_AAA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Rupture of the abdominal aortic aneurysm.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_RUPTURE_AIC</LocID>									<Text>Rupture Common Iliac Aneurysm</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_RUPTURE_AIC_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Rupture of the common iliac aneurysm.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
<!-- v0.02  -->
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_ISRA</LocID>											<Text>Adrenal crisis</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_ISRA_DESCRIPTION</LocID>								<Text>Adrenal crisis is a potentially life-threatening medical condition requiring immediate emergency treatment. It is a constellation of symptoms that indicate severe adrenal insufficiency caused by insufficient levels of the hormone cortisol.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_COMA_CETOACIDOSE</LocID>								<Text>DKA</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_COMA_CETOACIDOSE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>					<Text>Diabetic ketoacidosis (DKA) is a potentially life-threatening complication of diabetes.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_COMA_HYPEROSMOLAIRE</LocID>							<Text>HHS</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_COMA_HYPEROSMOLAIRE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Hyperosmolar hyperglycemic state (HHS) is a complication of diabetes.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
<!-- ++ v0.03 ++ -->
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_PURPURA_FULMINANS</LocID>							<Text>Purpura fulminans</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_PURPURA_FULMINANS_DESCRIPTION</LocID>				<Text>Purpura fulminans is an acute, often fatal, thrombotic disorder which manifests as blood spots, bruising and discolouration of the skin resulting from coagulation in small blood vessels within the skin and rapidly leads to skin necrosis. Purpura fulminans is a presenting feature of severe acute sepsis.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_CIVD</LocID>										<Text>DIC</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_CIVD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>							<Text>Disseminated intravascular coagulation (DIC) is a condition in which blood clots form throughout the body, blocking small blood vessels.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
<!-- ++ v0.03.2 ++ -->
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_PURPURA_THROMBOPENIQUE</LocID>					<Text>Severe thrombocytopenic purpura</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_PURPURA_THROMBOPENIQUE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>		<Text>Severe thrombocytopenia causes purpura: it is petechial, non-infiltrated, isolated or ecchymotic, sometimes associated with large hematomas. The discovery of a purpura requires the prescription of a blood count. The platelet count is usually less than 20 giga/L.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_DRESS_SD</LocID>									<Text>DRESS Syndrome</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_DRESS_SD_DESCRIPTION</LocID>						<Text>Drug reaction with eosinophilia and systemic symptoms (DRESS) syndrome, initially recognized as a serious form of cutaneous drug adverse reaction, is now viewed as a drug-related syndrome that can cause life-threatening organ dysfunctions.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_THROMBOPENIE_HEPARINE</LocID>						<Text>HIT</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_THROMBOPENIE_HEPARINE_DESCRIPTION</LocID>			<Text>Heparin-induced thrombocytopenia (HIT) is a rare drug-induced, immune-mediated prothrombotic disorder associated with thrombocytopenia and venous and/or arterial thrombosis. HIT results from a humoral immune reaction directed against a complex involving endogenous platelet factor 4 (PF4) and exogenous heparin: auto-antibodies recognize PF4 only when it is complexed with heparin. This immune complex activates the circulating platelets via their FcγRIIA surface receptors, leading to consumptive thrombocytopenia and hypercoagulability. The source of heparin (bovine >porcine), its formulation (unfractionated >low molecular weight >fondaparinux), the dose (prophylactic >therapeutic >heparin flushes), route of administration (subcutaneous >intravenous) and duration of administration (over 4 days >4 days or less) are determining factors.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
<!-- ++ v0.03.3 ++ -->
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_TRANSPLANTATION_COEUR</LocID>						<Text>Heart transplant</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			<GameDBLocalizedString>	<LocID>TRM_MOREDG_TRANSPLANTATION_COEUR_DESCRIPTION</LocID>			<Text>A heart transplant, or a cardiac transplant, is a surgical transplant procedure performed on patients with end-stage heart failure or severe coronary artery disease when other medical or surgical treatments have failed.</Text>	</GameDBLocalizedString>
			
		</LocalizedStrings>
    </GameDBStringTable>
</Database>